SHELDON:
Mm.
(Sheldon:)Well, this is very pleasant.
(Leonard:)I'm glad you're enjoying yourself.
And you said there would never
be enough pasta for the three of us.
(Leonard:)I stand corrected.
(Sheldon:)You know,
Italian housewives have a rule of thumb:
(Sheldon:)A handful of dry pasta
about an inch in diameter...
(Sheldon:)...is sufficient for each person,
as it doubles in volume when cooked.
(Steph:)That's very interesting.
(Penny:)- Thank you.
- She doesn't mean it. She's just being nice.
(Sheldon:)Well, Stephanie, since Leonard seems
to be dropping the conversational ball...
(Sheldon:)...I guess I'll just have to pick it up.
Ahem.
(Sheldon:)Have you ever witnessed a violent crime?
(Penny:)- No.
- Good.